我们要换掉那个
So we're gonna change that one.
我回来啦
I'm back.
快让我瞧瞧 快让我瞧瞧
Okay, let me see, let me see, let me see!
你们得戴上...
You guys are want to, um...
我滴神啊
Oh, my god!
爱死了
I love it!
没事儿了
All clear.
好了 所以...
Okay, so--
好棒啊 真的好棒啊
So good! It is so good!
过去几个月里
For the last few months,
小卡和我合力翻新一座老房子
Cam and I have been redoing a house together
我们会进行炒房活动
that we're gonna flip,
不得不说 进展非常顺利
and I have to say, it has been goin' great!
我们是绝佳组合
We make an amazing team.
-是啊 关键就是信任 -绝对的
- Yeah. The key is trust. - Absolutely.
关键在于 我让克莱尔以为是她在掌控大局
The key is, I let Claire think she's in charge.
我用更大更贵的东西掩藏我真正想要的
I hide what I want in something bigger and more expensive.
当她反对的时候
Then when she rejects that,
我们就能"妥协"成我一直想要的东西
we "compromise" on what I wanted all along.
我把这称为"特洛伊木马战术"
I call my method "The trojan horse."
知道我是怎么领养到莉莉的吗
You know how I got Lily?
我跟米奇说要领养三胞胎
I asked Mitchell for triplets.
你一定会爱死我挑的厨房台面砖
You are going to love what I found for the kitchen countertops.
来自意大利卡拉拉市
It's from Carrarra, Itlay.
米开朗基罗就是在那里找到大理石
It's where Michelangelo got the marble
雕刻出《大卫》的
to make the "David."
难怪大卫穿不起衣服呢
Now we know why the "David" couldn't afford any clothes.
好吧 其实
Okay, well, uh...
我还挑了这款
I also found this one.
稍微逊色一些 但没那么贵
It's not as nice, but it's less expensive.
这也超预算了 但是
Well, it's still over budget, but...
我觉得就这个吧
I guess it's okay.
对了 我们没买到你要的盥洗室设备
By the way, we couldn't get the powder room fixtures you wanted.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
超预算23% 也就是982美元
Well, they're 23%, or $982, over the budget.
记住 那块地方只占了
Keeping in mind, that space is only
1462平方英尺中的12%
12% of 1,462 square feet.
每次我要控制小卡的花销
Whenever I need to rein in Cam's spending,
我就运用我的"数据倾销"法
I employ something that I like to call "The number dump."
所以 除非你愿意从地板预算中
So... unless you wanna cut 16%,
削减16% 也就是1764美元
or $1,764 from somewhere in the flooring budget,
我们就还得削减4%
we've gotta find another 4% overall.
好吧 不 只要漂亮就行了 没关系
Yeah. No, as long as they're pretty, it's fine. It's fine.
昨天 我不小心说了个"十一十零五"
Yesterday, I accidentally said "Eleventy-five."
大家都知道我对这个项目有多认真
So everybody knows how hard I worked on that project.
我是说
I mean--
等等 你在干嘛
Hey, wait. What are you doing?
把糖放回罐子里啊
Trying to put the sugar back in the thing.
去拿扫帚扫掉吧
Well, just go get the broom.
给我一美元我就吃
I'll eat it for a dollar.
我说为赚钱吃东西该怎么着
What did I say about eating things for money?
要价得高 人们就会以为物有所值
Charge the most. Then people will think you're worth it.
没错 那至少得5美元
That's right. That's at least $5.
-他说的是一美元 -拿扫帚去
- Hey, he said a dollar. - Broom.
老爸 我找不到我的围巾了
Hey, dad, I can't find my scarf,
衣柜的灯也坏了
and the closet light's burnt out.
-那就换灯泡啊 -我够不着
- So just change it. - I can't reach it.
要是有什么魔法
Oh, if only there was some magical way
能让人接近天花板就好了
of getting up closer to the ceiling.
你刚刚说话的语气很像迪兰
Okay, now you just sound like Dylan.
我说的是梯子啦
I'm saying get a step stool.
一件一件来 好吗
One thing at a time, okay?
什么情况
What is happening?
我在扫地啊
I'm sweeping.
不 你这不是扫地
No, you're not sweeping.
而是把糖都扫分散了
You're just spreading it all around.
现在要我吃的话 收费得提高了
It's gonna cost more if you want me to eat it now.
那一刻我突然发现
That's when it hit me--
我的女儿们完全不会做家务
My daughters know nothing about home care and maintenance.
我不希望她们这么依赖
I don't want 'em to be dependent.
我该向她们展示一位自强自立的
It's up to me to show them what a modern,
现代女性该是什么样了
self-sufficient woman looks like.
小心点 继续这样下去
Careful. Keep that up,
他要打电话给车管局时 就会按"兔"键
he'll have to hit "Numero dos" when he calls the DMV.
等到他会打电话的时候
By the time, he's old enough to call,
会按数字键"万"
tt will be "Numero uno."
太好了 他来了
Ay, there he is.
曼尼 你为什么自己跑到外面去吃早餐
Manny, why did you have breakfast alone outside?
我喜欢吃露天早餐
I felt like eating breakfast alfresco.
意思是说他把裤子都脱了吗
Does that mean he had his pants off?
因为如果我不行 他也不行
Because if I can't, he can't.
杰 他这一整个星期都自己在外面吃饭
Jay, he's been eating outside on his own all week.
你觉得是不是因为我把注意力
Do you think that he feels left out
都集中到乔身上 他感觉受冷落了
because of all the attention I give Joe?
我也在想同样的事
You know, I've been wondering the same thing.
跟你说 不如今天下午就让我带乔
Tell you what--why don't I have some father-son time
享受父子时光
with Joe this afternoon
你去陪陪曼尼
and give you some time with Manny?
好啊 你真贴心
Ay, that's so sweet.
你可以带乔去上宝宝班
You can take Joe to his baby class.
歌洛莉亚 我觉得他知道该怎么做宝宝
Gloria, I think he already knows how to be a baby.
我爱你 但你这话我可笑不出来了
I love you, but I can't laugh at that again.
曼尼 你放学后我去接你
Manny, how about I pick you up after school,
我们享受一下母子专属时光怎么样
and we both have a special day?
我之前跟杰说过
Well, I did talk to Jay
要买票参加一个读书会的事儿
about getting some tickets for this reading.
什么读书会
What reading?
不是吧你
Seriously?
《大白鲸》的读书会啊
The stage reading of "Moby Dick"?
我昨天晚上跟你说的
I told you about it last night.
我完全记不起来了
I have zero recollection of this.
我就知道我不该给你倒第二杯威士忌
I knew I shouldn't have poured you that second Scotch.
抱歉 伙计 但我已经决定
Sorry, buddy, but I already committed
今天下午陪乔了
to spending the afternoon with Joe
好让你妈妈能多点时间陪陪你
so you and your mom could have more time together.
也许她能带你去
Hey, maybe she can take you.
-可以吗 老妈 -当然了 亲爱的
- Can we, mom? - Of course, mi amor.
今天是你的专属日 你想做什么都行
It's your special day. We'll do whatever you want.
太好了 这将成为你永生难忘的4小时
Great. This is gonna be four hours you'll never forget.
伙计 看来只剩我们"兔"了
Hey, buddy. Looks like it's just the dos of us.
我怎么觉得你好像暗中捣鬼了
Why do I feel that you did something shifty?
我毫不知情
I have no idea.
但说真的 这可不是你的优良品质
But I gotta say, it's not your best quality.
好了 亲爱的 祝你今天开心
All right, sweetie, you have a good day.
爸爸 看我玩手球吧
Watch me play handball, daddy.
好的
Oh, okay.
下一个
Next!
那是麦洛 他打败了所有人
That's Milo. He beats everybody.
下一个手下败将
Next loser!
-他真刻薄 -我看出来了
- He's mean. - Yeah, I'm gettin' that.
-下一个 -到你了
- Next! - That's you.
又是个女的
Another girl?
亲爱的 亲爱的
Hey, sweetie? Sweetie?
你一定会很棒的
You're gonna do great, okay?
你说是就是呗
If you say so.
下一个
Next!
麦洛 这是我的错
Uh, Milo? That-- that was my fault.
我分散了她的注意力
I distracted her,
所以或许可以让她再来一次
So maybe she could just go again?
不带重玩的 下一个
No do-overs. Next!
下一个是我 我把这个机会给她了
Well, I'm next, and I would like to give her my turn.
不许换人 你到底玩不玩
No switcheroos. Are you playing or not?
-不玩 -胆小鬼 下一个
- No. - Chicken. Next.
我痛恨恶霸 我恨他们一辈子
I hate bullies. I've hated them my whole life.
我从斯科特·杜肯 格雷戈·普奇科
I hated them when they were named Scott Dworkin
到凯蒂·格林伍德 全都恨
Or Greg Pechenko or Katie Greenwald.
你猜怎么着 我决定上阵
Okay, you know what? I'm gonna play.
可是 爸爸 他很厉害的
But, daddy, he's really good.
我也很厉害的
Well, I'm really good, too.
-可这是体育运动 -我可以的
- But it's a sport. - I got this.
你们唠完没
You done talking?
我们现在在学校较量最合适不过了
You know, it's really appropriate that we're at a school,
因为我要给你上上课[教训]
because I'm about to teach you a lesson.
下一个
Next!
好吧 对不起 亲爱的
All right. Sorry, sweetheart.
我送你去上课
Here, I'll walk you to class.
不用了 谢谢你 先生
No, thank you, mister.
但是
But...
你在干嘛
Whatcha doin'?
我觉得我有个想法
I think I have an idea.
每座房子都需要让人惊叹的"哇"元素 对不对
Okay. Every house needs a "Wow" factor, right?
这座院子缺少的是什么
What is the one thing this backyard is missing?
-一名够格的买家吗 -别说傻话
- A qualified buyer? - Now don't be silly.
不是的 应该是一个带火焰效果的水景
No. A water feature with a fire element.
天呐 不行
Oh, god, no.
拜托 只要设想一下
No, no, please. Now just imagine--
后边这一整面墙
This entire back wall
都被连接到蓄水池上 每隔15分钟就
cascading into a reservoir that erupts into flames
像火焰一样喷发出来 听起来怎么样
on the quarter hour. How does that sound?
听起来挺费钱
Like we need a white tiger.
也许我的野心太大了
Maybe I'm being a little ambitious.
那我们只做一对舞蹈喷泉好了
So let's just do a couple dancing water fountains,
-收工吧 -不 等一下 小卡
- call it a day. - No, wait. Cam, Cam, Cam.
那样也会让我们的景观预算
That's gonna still put us, like,
超出将近3500美元
$3,500 over our landscape budget.
现在比我之前预想的超了40-12%了
Right now, we're 40-12 percent higher than I thought
因为斯密特加上了8%的附加费
we'd be at this point because Smitty added that 8% surcharge.
不好意思 你刚才是说40-12%吗
I'm sorry--did you just say 40-12 percent?
没 我没说
Mm, no, I didn't.
你说了 你总是这样
Yes, you did. You do this all the time.
你总是拿数字砸我 吓唬我 糊弄我
You just throw numbers at me to frighten and confuse me.
我还一直以为我们合作得挺好
And here I thought we were working so well together,
原来你一直在暗中操纵
and you're just being manipulative.
那你呢 小卡
What about you, Cam?
故意挑那些昂贵不切实际的东西
Pitching these crazy, over-the-top ideas
那样你就能得到你真正想要的
just so you can slip in what you really want.
你竟然指责我对你实行特洛伊木马战术
Oh, how dare you accuse me of trojan horsing you.
你这招竟然还起名了
You have a name for it?
不是 我是说
No, I mean--
你知道吗 我才不要站在这里
You know what? I will not stand here
被你这样的人指责
and be accused by the likes of you.
如果这里有扇门 大小姐
And if there was a door here, missy,
我非当你面摔门不可
I would slam it in your face.
我还以为要等15分钟才会"发火"呢
I thought we weren't flaming till the quarter hour!
歌洛莉亚和曼尼把我和乔单独留在家里
Gloria and Manny left me alone with Joe,
那非常爽 但也就爽了20分钟左右
and it was great... for about 20 minutes.
然后这小家伙就开始折磨我了
then the little bugger turned on me.
我使劲浑身解数让他安静下来
I tried everything to calm him down--
轻摇他 拿奶瓶喂他
Bouncing. Bottle.
用亮色的东西逗他
Brightly colored objects.
用大瓶酒灌自己
Bigger bottle.
所以我决定采取"把他扔车里"的老招数
So I did the old "put him in the car" trick.
不过我还是能听到他在外面哭
But I could still hear him out there.
我是在开玩笑啦
I'm just kidding.
我带他去上课
I drove him to his little class,
不过我们还没到那里 他就睡着了
but he dozed off right before we got there.
或许他暗中偷学了杰·普里契特的妙招
Or he took a page from the Jay Pritchett playbook--
看到即将面对的悲惨处境 就假装睡着了
saw the crap he was in for and pretended to be asleep.
普里契特先生
Mr. Pritchett?
-是我 -我是瑞秋·莉兹
- Yeah. - Rachel Lissy.
克莱尔的高中同学 记得吗
Claire's friend from high school, remember?
我怎么可能忘呢
How could I forget?
你开着你那台小车把我家信箱撞倒了
You knocked down my mailbox with your k-car.
我再次道歉
Again, I apologize.
-你过得怎样 -好得不能再好了
- How you doin'? - Couldn't be better.
我都结婚15年了
I've been married for 15 years,
那两个大男孩是我儿子
Two great boys over there.
库珀 放开你弟弟
Cooper! Unhand your brother!
我正要带他们去看詹姆斯·邦德电影
I'm taking them to the James Bond movie,
他们不让我坐在他们旁边
and they don't want me to sit with them.
我真怀念小婴儿
I miss babies.
婴儿好玩多了
Oh, they're a lot of fun, huh?
-见到你真高兴 -见到你才叫高兴呢
- So nice to see you. - Nice seeing you.
挺好的孩子
Great kids.
不 不行
Ugh! No, you're not!
乔 我找了个更好的方式增进父子感情
Joe, I found a better way for us to bond...
詹姆斯·邦德[意译：增进感情]
James Bond.
我爸爸教会了我一切关于保修房子的事情
My dad taught me everything there is to know about maintaining a home,
今天 这一传统要传承下去
and today, that tradition continues.
瞧 灯泡换好了
Voila! Light bulb changed.
我有个想法
Hey, I have an idea.
我们一起了解下这幢房子
Let's get to know the house, huh?
我有个想法
Hey, I have an idea--
我们把他锁在里面吧
Let's lock him in.
快到这个宝贝东西这里来
Okay. Let's go over this baby right here.
我们看到的是什么
What are we lookin' at, huh?
光合作用
Photosynthesis?
某种意义上来说 是的
In a sense, yeah.
-是吗 -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah, yeah.
光合作用将二氧化碳
Uh, photosynthesis converts carbon dioxide
转化为植物的营养物质
into food for plants.
热水器将冷水转化成热水
This water heater converts cold water into hot.
什么东西能将我们的对话转成结束状态
What converts this conversation into over?
姑娘们 你们得学会这些东西
Girls, you need to learn these things.
终有一天你们会独自生活
You might find yourselves living alone at some point.
我期盼那一天的到来
I long for the day.
我们从一些最基础的开始 好吗
Okay, we're just gonna start with something really basic, all right?
我把指示灯给关了
I am turning the pilot light off.
这玩意儿偶尔会熄灭
These things go out occasionally.
-为什么 -我不知道 没有人知道
- Why? - I don't know. No one knows.
就当是小精灵干的好了
Let's just say gremlins do it.
如果这事发生在你们身上 怎么办
But if it happens to you, what do you do?
-叫个伙计来 -或妹子
- Call a guy. - Or a girl.
天啊 我们真的是在柜子里了[同性恋]
Oh, my god, we're literally in a closet,
-你还那么说 -集中注意力
- and you just said that. - Focus.
你们不需要叫任何人 重新点亮它
You don't call anyone. To re-light the pilot,
把阀转到"控制"
Turn the valve to "Pilot,"
按下去 让气流通
You press it down to begin the flow of gas,
等上那么几秒
You wait a few seconds...
你们是从哪个世界来的啊
Where you guys from originally?
按下点火器
And you just press the igniter.
好了
There you go.
真是奇怪 怎么不管用了
That's odd. Why is it not working?
我知道了
Oh, I got it.
我们何不直接从水龙头里接热水灌进去呢
Why don't we just fill it up with hot water from the tap?
又灭了一盏灯[蠢死]
Found another light that's out.
克莱尔和我在水景这事上陷入了僵局
Claire and I were at a stalemate on the water feature.
所以我请了一位有经验的专家过来
So I brought in an experienced professional
打破这种窘境
to help break the tie.
帕姆恰好是我的朋友
Pam also happens to be a friend
也是莉莉学校的同性恋家长
and a fellow gay parent at Lily's school.
我是想在背后做手脚 搞定克莱尔吗
Am I trying to stack the deck against Claire here?
不 我绝不会这么
No. I would never be so...
天才
genius.
克莱尔 这是帕姆
Oh. Oh, Claire, this is Pam.
-帕姆 这是克莱尔 -很高兴见到你
- Pam, Claire. - Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
-你好 -帕姆是有执照的承包商
- You, too. - Pam is a licensed contractor.
装修过很多房子
Done a lot of houses.
我觉得有第三方在这里挺好的
I thought it'd be nice to bring in a third party
会比较客观 帮忙解决喷泉纠纷
that's objective, to help settle the fountain dispute.
要客观 是啊
Oh. Objective, right.
我儿子和莉莉是同学
Well, my son does go to school with Lily,
但是相信我 这绝不会比你的美貌
but believe me, that is not gonna sway my decision
更影响我的决定
any more than the fact that you are beautiful.
谢谢 你也很美貌
Thank you. You are, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
我来帮你拿"罐子"[胸部]
Let me grab your cans.
你的油漆罐
Your paint cans.
好了
There you go.
那么
So...
怎么了呀 乔
Hey, what's the matter,Joe?
嘿 好小子 乖小子
Hey, that's a boy. That's a boy.
到这里来 来
Come here. There you go.
好了 好了
Here you are. There you go.
好了
There you go.
我很乐意带他出去 哄他不哭
You know, I'm happy to take him outside until he stops crying.
不不 我不希望你错过这电影
Oh, no, I wouldn't want you to miss this.
没关系 丹尼尔·克雷格不露肉
It's fine. Once Daniel Craig put his shirt back on,
-我就没兴趣了 -真的吗
- I lost interest. - Are you sure?
-真的 -好吧
- Absolutely. - Okay.
给 去吧 好小子
Here--just go ahead. Attaboy.
乖小子 谢谢你了
Attaboy. Thank you very much.
我就在外面
I'll be right outside.
-好的 -嘘
- Okay. - Shh!
你闭嘴 内森
You shush, Nathan!
笨东西
Stupid thing!
爸 我们站这好久了
Dad, we've been standing here forever.
就不能直接叫个伙计来修吗
Can't we just call the guy?
不 没什么伙计 我就是那个伙计
No. There is no guy. I'm the guy.
这是我需要你做的 跑去五金店
Here's what I need you to do. Run to the hardware store,
买个T6梅花螺丝刀回来
get me a T6 torx screwdriver.
-什么 -就问那伙计
- What? - Just ask the guy.
我以为那没有什么伙计
I thought there was no guy.
那有一个
There is one there!
-也有可能是妹子啊 -喏
- Could be a girl. - Eh?
快去
Just go!
我不需要梅花螺丝刀
I didn't need a torx screwdriver.
不过我一直都想要一个
I've always wanted one, though.
但我需要他们出去
But I needed them out of the house,
那么 我就可以 找个伙计
so... I could... call... a guy.
老爸 帮帮我
Dad, help me.
我们是又要看你在那儿
Are we gonna do that thing again
像《风月俏佳人》里一样试穿各种衣服吗
where you try on different outfits like in "Pretty Woman"?
我刚看见你很帅地投篮嘛 是吧
Saw you sinkin' some j's back there, huh?
1盯4联防 掩护俩人
Box and one. Cover two.
砍鲨战术 对不对
Sh-shaq-a-hack? Am I right?
根本不沾边
Not even close.
-什么事 -据江湖传闻
- What's up? - Well, word has it
你曾是一名优秀的手球运动员
that you were a pretty good handball player back in the day.
是啊
Yeah.
尼尔·阿姆斯特朗还曾是"优秀"喇叭手呢
And Neil Armstrong was a "pretty good" trumpet player.
我发现你在操场上待的时间
I see you spent a lot more time on the court
远比在教室长
than you did in the classroom,
所以很明显 我找对人了
So clearly, I've come to the right place.
听着 我需要你传授我你全部的球技
Look, I need you to teach me everything you know.
为什么这事那么重要
How come it's so important?
有个小孩
Well, there's this kid,
他欺负莉莉和她的同学
and he's been kind of bullying Lily and all her friends.
我试图教训他
And I tried to teach him.
想让他在手球场上安分点
I tried to put him in his place on the handball court,
结果失败了
and I lost.
我脑子里都是莉莉失望的眼神
And I-I could just see the disappointment in Lily's eyes.
说得好像她眼睛里有感情一样
Like there's any emotion in those eyes.
你要不要帮我
Are you gonna help me or not?
-好吧 -太棒了
- Okay. - Yes!
但我要你付出105%的努力
But I need you to give it 105%.
不 我付出110%的努力 哥们儿
Ah, no. It's 110%, buddy.
那不可能
That's impossible.
是的 喷泉是有些昂贵
Yes. I think the fountain's a little pricy.
但是 它的重要性简直无法忽视
But you know what? It's gonna more than make up for itself
因为当一家人走进房子
when a family comes in here
将被这个家迷得神魂颠倒
and falls head over heels in love with this home.
好吧 这点说得好
Okay, that's a valid point.
外面确实还有点儿空间
It is a bit of an empty space out there.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧 我知道你的意思
Well, I mean, I see what you're saying.
不好意思 这里面真热啊
Sorry. It's hot in here, right?
女人到了一定年纪就会出现你这情况
Oh, well, you know, that happens to women of a certain age,
我妈就是
Like with my mom.
不会吧 你才多少岁啊 35岁吧
Are you kidding? What are you, like, 35?
你也美丽动人啊 像个天使一样
What are you, like, an angel sent from heaven?
我知道你的意思
I see what you're saying.
我觉得这样价格太高 就没人会买了
I just feel that we might be pricing ourselves out of the market.
要是有户人家来了
If a family wants to come in here,
还想建一个喷泉
and--and build themselves a fountain,
他们可以自己建啊
They can do so themselves.
确实啊
That's true.
好吧 帕姆 你知道的
Um, okay, well, you know, Pam,
有很多像我们这样的家庭
Um, there are lots of families like...ours...
他们搬过来 是因为这里的学校好
Moving to this neighborhood for the schools.
插一句 我看过康纳的艺术作品 太美了
P.S., saw Connor's art project--gorgeous.
不愧是才艺世家啊
Talent runs in the family.
总之 我觉得 如果后院做得有趣点儿
Anyway, I'm just saying I think a family would respond
一定会打动人家
to having a little drama in the backyard.
我看帕姆已经把意见说得很清楚了 对吧
I think Pam's made it pretty clear what she likes. Am I right?
糟了
Oh, no.
我的衣服都是通透的了
Now my shirt is all see-through.
你的花招也被看透了
And so are you.
你不会被这种"美人计"给迷住了吧
Please tell me you are not falling for this.
不会 但我看得非常过瘾
I'm not, but I am enjoying this little show tremendously,
所以谢谢啦
So thank you.
话说回来 我从专业角度对喷泉的意见是
As for my professional opinion on the fountain,
别做了
don't do it.
如果是你们自己住的
I mean, if you were gonna live here yourself,
那我会赞同 但那东西太贵了
I'd say go for it. But it's too expensive for a flip.
就是呀 就是呀
Yeah. Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
-小卡 -好吧
- Cam? - Fine.
该死的拉拉
Lesbians.
我不敢相信我竟然陪亲儿子一起买吊袜带了
I can't believe I just went garter shopping with my son.
如果你有更好的办法让袜子不往下掉
When you find a better way to keep my socks up,
告诉我一声
let me know.
既然我们都来商城了
Hey, as long as we're in the mall,
要不去婴儿乐园看看杰和乔吧
you wanna stop in the baby class to see Jay and Joe?
别了 让他俩好好培养感情吧
No. They need this time to make a connection.
父子关系可不像母子关系
It's not like mother and son,
不是生来就那么强烈的
that the bond is naturally strong.
嘿 那不是乔吗
Hey, isn't that Joe over there?
不 那是别家的小屁孩
No, that's some weird baby.
他才没我家乔那么完美呢
He's not perfect like my little Joe.
但他的毯子一模一样呢
But he's got the same blanket.
歌洛莉亚 你在这儿干嘛
Gloria. What are you doing here?
你怎么能把宝宝交给陌生人
You gave our baby to a stranger?!
她不是陌生人 她是克莱尔的朋友
She's not a stranger. She's Claire's friend.
-嘘 -闭嘴 内森
- Shh! - Shut up, Nathan!
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
爸 煤气开了
The gas is on, dad.
点火器有火花了
I can see the spark from the igniter.
我不知道那是什么玩意儿
I don't know what it is.
那是热电偶
That's your thermocouple.
里面积了沉淀物
You get a little sediment in there
或者是铁锈 就不好用了
or some rust, and you're done for.
原来是热电偶的问题啊
The thermocouple. Of course.
我怎么没想到
Why didn't I think of that?
谢啦 爸 这点小事不该打扰你的
Thanks, dad. I-I shouldn't be buggin' you with this stuff.
你开什么玩笑 我最乐于助人了
Are you kiddin' me? I love to help.
让我觉得你还需要我
Makes me feel like you still need me.
我当然需要你
Of course I need you.
你总是这些问题的专家
You're the best when it comes to this.
还有什么要修的吗
Anything else you need fixin'?
有啊 事实上
Yeah, actually,
我的大拇指坏了
I've been havin' a little trouble with my thumb.
老伙计啦 那个好修
Oh, the old thumb. That's simple.
只要把它摁回去 然后"啵"一声就好了
Just push it back in and make that popping sound.
-好啦 你这办法好 -修好啦
- Oh, yeah, you're right. - There you go.
今晚记得对克莱尔说她很美
Make sure you tell Claire how pretty she looks tonight.
女人就爱听这个
A woman needs to hear that.
你也要对妈说说
You do the same with mom.
别了 你妈妈厌烦了
No, your mom's a little tired of
我经常对她说克莱尔很美
hearing how pretty Claire is.
说得好
Good one!
好吧 爱你哦
All right. Love you.
我也爱你哦
Love you, too.
爸 我们回来啦
Dad, we're home.
这真是最无聊的一次购物
That was the least fun I have ever had shopping ever.
给你
Here.
宝贝 这是扭力扳手 不是十字螺丝刀
Honey, that's a torque wrench, not a torx screwdriver.
好吧 你就嚷嚷吧
Okay, you're just screaming now.
你不能自己去买吗 你可是行家啊
Can't you just go get it? You're the best at this stuff.
就是啊 还有 车子也有点儿问题
Yeah, plus the car is doing something funny,
而且仪表盘上有个
and there's a light on the dashboard
像小油灯一样的指示灯亮了
that looks like a little genie lamp.
我家孩子不能自立 但也许那没关系
My kids are helpless, but maybe that's okay.
因为多年以后 等他们有了自己的房子
Because years from now when they have their own houses,
他们会用超炫的高科技视频电话打给我
they'll call me on their hologram phones
然后说 "老爸救命 只能靠你了"
and say, "Help me, dad. You're my only hope."
我就会成为第7区最幸福的老爸
And I'll be the happiest father in Sector 7...
或者是第12区 如果我们混得很好的话
or Sector 12, if we're doing really well.
搞不懂你妈怎么这么恼火
I don't know why your mom's so mad.
可能是因为
Maybe it has something to do
你把宝贝儿子交给陌生人了
with giving your son away to a complete stranger.
接下来就把你送出去
You're next.
话说回来 你俩去商城干嘛
And what were you two doing in the mall, anyway?
你俩不是去看《大白鲸》吗
I thought you were seeing "Moby Dick."
票都卖完了
It was sold out.
可能你能这样讨好她
Maybe that's how you can make it up to her--
明天替她带我去参加《白鲸记》阅读会
Take me to the "Moby dick" reading tomorrow.
想得美
Nice try.
无私地帮助她另一个儿子
Doing something selfless for her other son
能够弥补你这回犯下的滔天大罪
could make up for your monumental blunder.
送花和珠宝可能管用
Maybe flowers or jewelry.
我喜欢用钱来解决问题
I like to throw money at the problem.
你好呀 美女
Hello, pretty lady.
晚饭想吃什么啊
What do you wanna do for dinner?
不如用宝宝换一张披萨饼吧
How about we exchange the baby for a cheese pizza?
-还在生气吗 -我打电话订票去
- Is this about today? - I'll call for those tickets.
你本来应该和宝宝共度美好的亲子时光
You were supposed to spend quality time with the baby.
乔睡着了
Joe was asleep.
他根本不知道自己错过了木偶剧
He didn't even know he missed the puppet show.
那叫"婴儿教学班"
It was the baby class!
好 你愿意怎么叫都行
Okay, call it what you want.
我只看到一个嬉皮士手里拿着只青蛙
I saw a hippie with a frog on his hand.
另外跟你说一声
And for your information,
我明天会带曼尼去那个朗读会
I'm takin' Manny to that reading tomorrow.
你现在只是在想办法给自己解围
Now you're just trying to dig yourself out of a hole
因为你知道自己的谎言被拆穿了
because you know that you were caught in a lie.
-有件怪事 -等会儿再说 曼尼
- So here's something... - Not now, manny.
让他说
Oh, let him talk.
我给剧场打了电话
I called the theater,
他们说明天的演出还有很多票没卖出去
and they have tons of tickets for tomorrow's show.
而且今天的演出门票也没有卖光
And it turns out today's show wasn't sold out, either.
-曼尼 现在不是说这个的时候 -让他说
- Ay, Manny, not now. - Let him talk.
妈 你为什么说票卖光了
Mom, why'd you say it was sold out?
是啊 你为什么说票卖光了
Yeah. Why'd you say it was sold out?
我搞错了嘛 英语不是我的母语
It was a mistake. This is not my first language.
我不怎么懂英语滴
I don't understand English very goodly.
别打语言牌
Don't play that card.
你跟我一样不想陪他去
You didn't wanna go any more than I did.
好吧 我说了谎 但我有资格说谎
Fine. I lied, but I earned that lie.
曼尼 我很抱歉
Ay, Manny, I am so sorry.
但你知道我一直努力为这个家里每个人
But you know that I am always trying to do everything
尽心尽力 无微不至
for everybody in this family.
但你呢
But you.
你只考虑你自己
You only do what's good for you.
我告诉你吧 杰·普里契特
Let me tell you something, Jay Pritchett--
在抚养孩子这件事上
When it comes to raising kids,
种什么 得什么
you get what you give.
你这英语倒是说得挺好的
Well, you rattled that off pretty goodly.
你没必要这么做的 爸爸
You don't have to do this, daddy.
我知道 但爸爸很想这么做 好吗
I know, but daddy really wants to do this, okay?
不不不
No, no, no.
不行 你想干什么 萨迪
No, what do you think you're doing, Sadie?
不许插队 回去
No cutsies. Come on.
下一个
Next.
你好 麦洛
Hello, Milo.
你好 莉莉的爸爸之一
Hello, one of Lily's dads.
好 我们玩点刺激的吧 好吗
All right, let's make this interesting, okay?
如果我赢 就实行新规矩 好吗
If I win, the new rule is this, okay?
任何选手都不能连续玩三个回合以上
No player can play more than three times in a row
一定要回去重新排队
without getting back in line
给其他孩子上场的机会
and letting the other kids play.
-要是我赢呢 -那我就给你两万块
- What if I win? - Then I'll give you $20,000.
-来吧 -好 我们开始
- You're on. - All right. Let's do this.
好耶
Yes!
我得一分
One point for me.
我得一分 没错
One point for me. That's right.
麦洛 墙在这边呢
Milo, the wall's over here.
不行不行 这个不算 出界了
Nah, nah. Doesn't count. It was out.
太高了你够不着是吧
Little too high for you, huh?
球弹三次墙壁 你个败寇
Three bounces to the wall, makes you a lo-ser,
你个败寇
makes you a lo-ser.
最后一分 我得到就是我赢
Final point. I get this, I win.
老天爷子保佑我
Oh, sweet lord jesus.
好耶 好耶 我赢了
Whoo! Yes! Yes! Winner!
冠军是我 我是冠军
cham-pi-on! Cham-pi-on!
这阵子得让小卡负责接送莉莉了
Cam's gonna be doing drop-offs for a while.
我们收到了警告信
We got a letter.
我相信你们都在琢磨
I'm sure you're both wondering
我为什么今晚召集你们来这里
why I summoned you here tonight.
现在我将呈上让人惊叹的"哇"元素
I now present to you the "Wow" factor.
小卡
Cam...
我简直不敢相信你居然擅自做主了
I cannot believe that you went rogue.
太不够意思了 我支持克莱尔
Uncool. I am with Claire on this.
你们很快就会明白原因
You'll soon see why.
准备好欣赏...
Prepare your senses...
会跳舞的水吧
for dancing waters.
-哇 -哇
- Wow. - Wow.
"哇"之元素
Factor.
现在想象一个潜在买家
Now imagine a prospective buyer,
被这水芭蕾迷得神魂颠倒
so entranced by the aqua ballet,
于是当即决定花大价钱买下这房子
they're compelled instantly to make a rich offer.
我甚至还在池子里装满了
I've even stocked the pools
金子做的鱼
with fish of gold.
其实就是金鱼
They're just goldfish,
但它们...它们就在这里
But they're-- they're right here.
这...这真的很惊艳 小卡
This is... this is really impressive, Cam.
你花了多少钱
What did you spend?
实际上 没少花 但我不想说钱的事
Quite a bit, actually, but I don't wanna get into that.
让我把功率提高到"十一十五"
Let me turn this up to eleventy-five.
-哇 -哇
- Wow. - Wow.
"哇"之元素
Factor.
小卡 这些金鱼
Hey, Cam, are fish of gold
这样倒着游正常吗
supposed to swim backwards like that?
不 据我所知 不正常
No, not to my knowledge, no.
是哦 它们好像都...
Yeah, it's kind of like they're all--
它们都在往那东西上聚集
They're gathering towards that thing.
好像...天呐
It's like a-- oh, no!
它们都被吸出来了
They are getting sucked out.
你把小鱼们害死了
You're killing them!
克莱尔 快把插销拔了
Claire! Unplug it!
这是半截金鱼 半截金鱼啊
It's half a fish! That's a half a fish!
在我们谓之生活的大染缸中
There are certain queer times and occasions
总有些奇怪的时间和场合
in this strange, mixed affair we call life...
当一个人把整个世界
When a man takes this whole universe
看作一个巨大的笑话
for a vast practical joke...
尽管那略显智慧 但他却并未察觉
Though the wit thereof he but dimly discerns...
嘀嘀嘀 嘀嘀嘀嘀
Tick-tick-tick, tick-tick-tick-tick,
看爷叱诧球场
Goes the dynamite,
看爷笑傲江湖
goes the dynamite!
他竟然毫不怀疑 那个笑话
And more than suspects that the joke
其实嘲弄的是他自己 而非别人
is at nobody's expense but his own.
-好 闭上眼睛 -为什么
- All right. Close your eyes. - Why?
-相信我 -好吧
- Just trust me. - Okay.
球场上永远不能闭眼
Never close your eyes on the court!
-但你让我闭上 -不能让我影响到你
- But you told me... - Don't let me get in your head!
戳破它们
Pop 'em!
在泡泡落地前戳破它们 快点
Pop 'em all before they hit the ground! Go!
我不是很明白该怎么戳
I don't really understand how...
握拳 把拇指放在边上
Make a fist with your thumb on the side.
现在把拇指放到前面
Now bring your thumb to the front.
好 再做一遍
Okay, now do it again.
你刚刚用手语比了"屁股"
You just spelled "Ass" in sign language.
好 闭上眼睛
Okay. Close your eyes.
没事的 我们不在场上了
It's okay. We're off the court.
你永远都在场上
You're never off the court!